NATALIA W KUKULA

Github: github.com/nataliakukula Email: kuki kukula@yahoo.com **Phone:** 312-709-6145 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/nataliakukula

Portfolio: whispering-sierra-39902.herokuapp.com Chicago, IL 60613

Web Developer with an educational background in public relations and media marketing, experience in hospitality and advertising, which led to gaining high level communication skills, detail-orientedness, entrepreneurial interest towards human-centered design.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, mySQL, mongoDB, Express, Handlebars, React.js, jQuery

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Mindful Plate - Fullstack Collaborative Project

- App that utilizes drag and drop and teaches users about portion control
- Built with: MongoDB, Express, React.JS, Node.JS, Firebase Authentication
- Code: https://github.com/nataliakukula/mindful-plate
- Website: https://powerquartet.herokuapp.com/

SoundCloud Scraper - Scraping to MongoDB

- App build for scraping headless and dynamic HTML
- Built with: Puppeteer, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery & MongoDB
- Code: https://github.com/nataliakukula/mongo-scraper
- Website: https://lit-inlet-10505.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

Certificate - Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp Northwestern University, Chicago, IL

August 2018 – March 2019

Master's Degree - Journalism, Public Relations and Media Marketing

University of Warsaw, Warsaw, Poland

October 2011 – October 2014

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Guest Experience Manager

Ginosi Apartels, Chicago, Illinois, US. March 2017 – August 2018

- Follow policy while multi-tasking through company's software.
- Support headquarters to fulfill customer service requests.
- Provide staff training, inspect work, hire team members per human resources' request.
- Report any guest, staff, apartment, software issues to line manager daily.
- Create processes and documentation to make inventory levels (PAR) more efficient.

Guest Service Host

Ivy Boutique Hotel, Chicago, Illinois, US. February 2017 – July 2018

- Register and process guests to their assigned rooms and handle payments.
- Accommodate guest requests and provide concierge assistance.
- Communicate with hotel staff on the status of guest rooms.
- Multi-task through different computer systems such as InnRoad, Saflok, HelloShift etc.
- Make reservations, upselling guest rooms and promote hotel services.

Front Desk Manager

Dream Hostel Warsaw, Dream Hostels LTD., Warsaw, Poland May 2016 – January 2017

- Work on the opening team to startup a new chain hostel and create efficient processes.
- Hiring, training, team building, scheduling, evaluating, supervising staff and events.
- Assist with operations and cooperate with the central office to manage reservations.
- Focus on customer satisfaction while upholding hostel standards.
- Help achieve Trip Advisor's star of excellence of 2016 within 8 months of operating and become the best hostel in Warsaw.

Advertising Representative

Tribune Publishing, Chicago, Illinois, USA January 2015 – January 2016

- Fulfill customer's requests for over 35 different publications (i.e. Chicago Tribune).
- Multi-task through different applications such as Adit, SharePoint and Microsoft Office.
- Aid customers in locating ads through <u>www.legacy.com</u> and MerlinOne E-sheets.
- Utilize soft sale techniques to aid customers in finding the correct products.
- Give a 100% to achieve largest revenue on the team and receive an award for making almost \$250,000 in quarter II.